{
    "subject": "resource/Jerry_Rubin",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Jerry Clyde Rubin (July 14, 1938 \u2013 November 28, 1994) was an American social activist, anti-war leader, and counterculture icon during the 1960s and 1970s. During the 1980s, he became a successful businessman.",
    "human_readable": "Jerry Rubin was an American social activist, anti-war leader, and counterculture icon during the 1960s and 1970s, and later became a successful businessman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9425133466720581,
            "question": "During which decades was Jerry Rubin an active social activist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7705668210983276,
            "question": "What role did Jerry Rubin play in the counterculture movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642440795898438,
            "question": "Can you describe Jerry Rubin's impact on American society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7521994113922119,
            "question": "What are some examples of Jerry Rubin's actions as a social activist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7272012233734131,
            "question": "What was Jerry Rubin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6700932383537292,
            "question": "Was Jerry Rubin's involvement primarily focused on political or social causes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6338075995445251,
            "question": "Besides activism, what other career path did Jerry Rubin pursue later in life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5590284466743469,
            "question": "What were some of the key beliefs or values that guided Jerry Rubin's activism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.550866425037384,
            "question": "What type of events or movements was Jerry Rubin associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5254225134849548,
            "question": "How is Jerry Rubin remembered by history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jerry Rubin was an American social activist, anti-war leader, and counterculture icon during the 1960s and 1970s, and later became a successful businessman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5638_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of events or movements was Jerry Rubin associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5638_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the key beliefs or values that guided Jerry Rubin's activism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5638_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides activism, what other career path did Jerry Rubin pursue later in life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5638_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5638_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information supporting that Jerry Rubin was indeed an American social activist, anti-war leader, and counterculture icon during the 1960s and 1970s, and later became a successful businessman."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}